iflickz.com 2013-05-25

# Privacy - iFlickz

Please read below the privacy statement of iFlickz.com, which demonstrates our site’s commitment to privacy. We want to provide a secure environment for all users of our web site. This policy applies only to iFlickz.com and not to other companies’ or organizations’ web sites to which we link.

**Information Not Shared with Third Parties**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. Your IP address or demographic information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.

**Providing personal details**

You may provide us with certain information such as your name, email address, postal address when registering for certain services such as contests and promotions. This information will primarily be used for the purpose of providing personalization and verification.

**Contests**

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information. The users’ contact information is used by us to contact the visitor when necessary, primarily to announce new contests, contest results and site features.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. iFlickz.com uses cookies to track user traffic patterns and for the personalization feature.

**Advertisers**

We work with various third party advertising networks. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by advertising network, and we do not have any access to this information.

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. iFlickz.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We make every effort to maintain quality of service and prevent misuse.

**Children’s Guidelines ( Children under 13 )**

This site collects and uses personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. This site allows children to post or distribute any personally identifiable information without first obtaining verifiable parental consent.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web Site, you can contact us at any point of time.
